Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- People, circa 1910-1971, I.; 1199 photographs
  - Boris Christoff as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 3, Item C03-040)
  - Boris Christoff as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 3, Item C03-041)
  - Boris Christoff and Margherita Roberti in Verdi's Don Carlos, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 3, Item C03-042)
  - Boris Christoff as King Philippe II with Jussi Bjorling as Don Carlos, 1957 Nov., 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 3, Item C03-043)
  - Fausto Cleva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-044)
  - Fausto Cleva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-045)
  - Fausto Cleva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-046)
  - Fausto Cleva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-047)
  - Van Cliburn, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Grab, Richard (Box 3, Item C03-048)
  - Van Cliburn, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-049)
  - Van Cliburn, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-050)
  - Andre Cluytens, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-051)
  - Clipping about Andre Cluytens, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-052)
  - Eugene Conley as Duke of Mantua, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-053)
  - Eugene Conley in the Barber of Seville?, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-054)
  - Eugene Conley as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-055)
  - Eugene Conley, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-056)
  - Eugene Conley and Winifred Heidt, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-057)
  - Nadine Conner as Rosina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-058)
  - Nadine Conner as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-059)
  - Nadine Conner, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-060)
  - Franco Corelli as Calaf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 3, Item C03-061)
  - Franco Corelli as Calaf, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 3, Item C03-062)
  - Franco Corelli as Calaf with Birgit Nilsson as Turandot and Alessio de Paolis as the Emperor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 3, Item C03-063)
  - Fernando Corena as Bartolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-064)
  - Fernando Corena as Lescaut, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-065)
  - Fernando Corena as Don Pasquale, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-066)
  - Fernando Corena as Bartolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-067)
  - Fernando Corena as Gianni Schicchi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 3, Item C03-068)
  - Jon Crain as Turiddu, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-069)
  - Richard Crooks as Romeo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-070)
  - Mary Curtis-Verna as Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-071)
  - Mary Curtis-Verna as Leonora in Il Trovatore, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 3, Item C03-072)
  - Clifford Curzon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-073)
  - Clifford Curzon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-074)
  - Gyorgy Cziffra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-075)
  - Frederick Dalberg as Landgraf Hermann in Tannhauser, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-001)
  - Irene Dalis as Laura in La Gioconda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-002)
  - Irene Dalis as Brangane in Tristan und Isolde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-003)
  - Lawrence Davidson as Benoit in La Boheme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-004)
  - Gloria Davy as Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-005)
  - Desire Defauw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Dewey, Anne Pilger (Box 4, Item C04-006)
  - Ms. note from Desire Defauw, 1955 March 26, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-007)
  - Lisa Della Casa as Eva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-008)
  - Lisa Della Casa as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-009)
  - Lisa Della Casa in Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 4, Item C04-010)
  - Lisa Della Casa as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-011)
  - Lisa Della Casa as Donna Elvira, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-012)
  - Lisa Della Casa as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-013)
  - Lisa Della Casa as Arabella, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 4, Item C04-014)
  - Vivian Della Chiesa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-015)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Canio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-016)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Pollione, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-017)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-018)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-019)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Ernani, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 4, Item C04-020)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Lohengrin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-021)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Lohengrin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-022)
  - Mario Del Monaco as Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-023)
  - Alessio de Paolis as Don Basilio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-024)
  - Alessio de Paolis as Alcindoro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-025)
  - Alessio de Paolis as Spoletta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-026)
  - Victor De Sabata, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 4, Item C04-027)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Canio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 4, Item C04-028)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-029)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-030)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Duke of Mantua, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-031)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Don Jose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-032)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Duke of Mantua, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-033)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Pinkerton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-034)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Pinkerton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-035)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Des Grieux (Manon), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Luxardo (Box 4, Item C04-036)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Canio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-037)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Radames, 1956-1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-038)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Riccardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-039)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Nemorino, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 4, Item C04-040)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Canio with Tito Gobbi as Tonio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 4, Item C04-041)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Pinkerton with Renata Tebaldi as Cio-Cio San, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 4, Item C04-042)
  - Giuseppe Di Stefano as Pinkerton with Renata Tebaldi as Cio-Cio San, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 4, Item C04-043)
  - Mattiwilda Dobbs as Lucia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-044)
  - Mattiwilda Dobbs as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 4, Item C04-045)
  - Mattiwilda Dobbs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-046)
  - Erno Dohnanyi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 4, Item C04-047)
  - Pino Donati, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-048)
  - Antal Dorati, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-049)
  - Antal Dorati, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-050)
  - Antal Dorati, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-051)
  - Rafael Druian, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-052)
  - Nelson Eddy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-053)
  - Otto Edelmann as Hans Sachs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-054)
  - Otto Edelmann as Baron Ochs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 4, Item C04-055)
  - Otto Edelmann as Der Wanderer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-056)
  - Otto Edelmann as Baron Ochs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 4, Item C04-057)
  - Rosalind Elias as Lola, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-058)
  - Rosalind Elias as Erika, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-059)
  - Rosalind Elias as Cherubino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-060)
  - Rosalind Elias as Suzuki, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 4, Item C04-061)
  - Rosalind Elias as Nancy, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 4, Item C04-062)
  - Mischa Elman, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Beausacq, Ingeborg de (Box 4, Item C04-063)
  - Cloe Elmo as Azucena, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-064)
  - Alberto Erede, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-065)
  - Wilhelm Ernest as Tannhäuser, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item C04-066)
  - Lucia Evangelista as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 4, Item C04-067)
  - Iurii Fedorovich Faier and Yuri Gregorovich at Bolshoi Ballet rehearsal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-001)
  - Eileen Farrell as Leonora in Il Trovatore, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 5, Item C05-002)
  - Eileen Farrell as Medee, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 5, Item C05-003)
  - Eileen Farrell as La Gioconda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-004)
  - Eileen Farrell as Alcestis, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-005)
  - Geraldine Farrar with dachsunds, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-006)
  - Jean Fenn as Musetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 5, Item C05-007)
  - Jean Fenn as Rosalinde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-008)
  - Eugenio Fernandi as the Duke of Mantua, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-009)
  - Eugenio Fernandi as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-010)
  - Eugenio Fernandi as Pinkerton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-011)
  - Eugenio Fernandi as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-012)
  - Kathleen Ferrier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-013)
  - Kathleen Ferrier as Orfeo, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Lend (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 5, Item C05-014)
  - Kathleen Ferrier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-015)
  - Kathleen Ferrier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Vivienne (London, England) (Box 5, Item C05-016)
  - Kathleen Ferrier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 5, Item C05-017)
  - Arthur Fiedler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-018)
  - Arthur Fiedler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-019)
  - Arthur Fiedler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 5, Item C05-020)
  - Typescript note from Arthur Fiedler, 1951 Dec. 3, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-021)
  - Arthur Fiedler with Pres. Dwight Eisenhower, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-022)
  - Typescript note from secretary to President Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1957 May 17, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-023)
  - Arthur Fiedler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-024)
  - Arthur Fiedler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-025)
  - Rudolf Firkusny, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Grab, Richard (Box 5, Item C05-026)
  - Rudolf Firkusny, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 5, Item C05-027)
  - Article about Rudolph Firkusny, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-028)
  - Sylvia Fisher as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sharland, Helga (Box 5, Item C05-029)
  - Sylvia Fisher as Kostelnicka, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-030)
  - Kirsten Flagstad as Leonore in Fidelio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-031)
  - Kirsten Flagstad, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-032)
  - Leon Fleisher, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-033)
  - Pierre Fournier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-034)
  - Carol Fox, General manager of Lyric Theater of Chicago, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-035)
  - Carol Fox (right) with Lawrence Kelly and unidentified employee of Lyric Theater of Chicago, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-036)
  - Virgil Fox, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 5, Item C05-037)
  - Zino Francescatti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-038)
  - Paul Franke as Panatellas in La Perichole, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-039)
  - Ferdinand Frantz as Wotan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-040)
  - Mirella Freni as Elisabeth de Valois with Nicolai Ghiaurov as King Philippe II in Don Carlos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-041)
  - Ferenc Fricsay, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Goldstein, Jet (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 5, Item C05-042)
  - Wilhelm Furtwängler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-043)
  - Wilhelm Furtwängler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-044)
  - Amelita Galli-Curci rehearsing with Homer Samuels, 1936 Nov. 15, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-045)
  - Amelita Galli-Curci, 1937, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-046)
  - Rudolph Ganz, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Blackstone Studios (Box 5, Item C05-047)
  - Rudolph Ganz, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-048)
  - Rudolph Ganz, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Keystone (Los Angeles, Calif.) (Box 5, Item C05-049)
  - Maria Teresa Garatti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-050)
  - Raya Garbousova, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-051)
  - Mary Garden, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Forbes (Box 5, Item C05-052)
  - Mary Garden, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-053)
  - Ms. note from Mary Garden, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-054)
  - Gianandrea Gavazzeni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-055)
  - Gianandrea Gavazzeni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-056)
  - Gianandrea Gavazzeni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 5, Item C05-057)
  - Nicolai Gedda as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rydberg, Enar M (Box 5, Item C05-058)
  - Nicolai Gedda as Don Ottavio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-059)
  - Nicolai Gedda as Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-060)
  - Nicolai Gedda as Anatol in Vanessa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-061)
  - Nicolai Gedda as Des Grieux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 5, Item C05-062)
  - Leyla Gencer as Francesca da Rimini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 5, Item C05-063)
  - Dusolina Giannini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-001)
  - Dusolina Giannini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-002)
  - Walter Gieseking, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lipnitzki (Paris, France) (Box 6, Item C06-003)
  - Walter Gieseking, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Carmen (Box 6, Item C06-004)
  - Walter Gieseking, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lipnitzki (Paris, France) (Box 6, Item C06-005)
  - Beniamino Gigli as Vasco di Gama, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 6, Item C06-006)
  - Beniamino Gigli as Nemorino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Edwards, Carlo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 6, Item C06-007)
  - Printed thank you note from Beniamino Gigli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-008)
  - Beniamino Gigli as Enzo Grimaldi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 6, Item C06-009)
  - Beniamino Gigli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lo Bianco, Palermo (Box 6, Item C06-010)
  - Drawing of Beniamino Gigli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Zanoni (Box 6, Item C06-011)
  - Emil Gilels, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-012)
  - Typescript note from Emil Gilels, 1955 Oct. 31, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-013)
  - Emil Gilels, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lipnitzki (Paris, France) (Box 6, Item C06-014)
  - Jack Gilford as Frosch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-015)
  - Carlo Maria Giulini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-016)
  - Tito Gobbi as Baron Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-017)
  - Tito Gobbi as Marcello, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Locchi (Box 6, Item C06-018)
  - Tito Gobbi as Wozzeck, 1951-1952, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 6, Item C06-019)
  - Tito Gobbi as Iago, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Locchi (Box 6, Item C06-020)
  - Tito Gobbi as Renato in Ballo in Maschera, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 6, Item C06-021)
  - Clipping about Tito Gobbi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-022)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 6, Item C06-023)
  - Tito Gobbi as Iago, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Harth (Wiesbaden, Germany) (Box 6, Item C06-024)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-025)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-026)
  - Tito Gobbi as Tonio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-027)
  - Tito Gobbi as Sheriff Jack Rance, 1956 Feb., 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 6, Item C06-028)
  - Tito Gobbi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 6, Item C06-029)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff with Giulietta Simionato as Dame Quickly, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 6, Item C06-030)
  - Tito Gobbi, Giulietta Simionato, Maria Caniglia, and Renata Tebaldi in Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-031)
  - Tito Gobbi as Figaro with Giulietta Simionato as Rosina, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 6, Item C06-032)
  - Tito Gobbi as Rigoletto with Anna Moffo as Gilda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 6, Item C06-033)
  - Tito Gobbi as Rodrigo with Richard Tucker as Don Carlos, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 6, Item C06-034)
  - Szymon Goldberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Particam Pictures (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 6, Item C06-035)
  - Vladimir Golschmann, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sherman, Editta (Box 6, Item C06-036)
  - Christel Goltz as Salome, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-037)
  - Igor Gorin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 6, Item C06-038)
  - Morton Gould, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-039)
  - Uta Graf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 6, Item C06-040)
  - Percy Grainger, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-041)
  - Arthur Grumiaux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-042)
  - Frank Guarrera as Escamillo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 6, Item C06-043)
  - Frank Guarrera as Valentin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 6, Item C06-044)
  - Frank Guarrera as Count Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-045)
  - Frank Guarrera as Marcello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-046)
  - Frank Guarrera as Marcello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-047)
  - Frank Guarrera as Escamillo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 6, Item C06-048)
  - Frank Guarrera as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 6, Item C06-049)
  - Frank Guarrera as Fritz Falke, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 6, Item C06-050)